Reihaneh Sadat-Shokouhi

Front-end developer

 ▼ Tehran, Iran
 ▼ r.sadatshokouhi@gmail.com
 ↓ +989927961998
 ## 01 Dec 2000
 ♠ sr-ssh

■ R_SadatShokouhi in Reihaneh Sadat Shokouhi

→ r.sadatshokouhi

Profile

Motivated, dedicated, and experienced front-end developer adept in all stages of advanced web development. Knowledgeable in the user interface, testing, and debugging processes. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

Skills (experienced)

JavaScript

- Reactis
- Nodejs
- Nextjs
- TypeScript

HTML

CSS

SASS

CSS frameworks

- Bootstrap
- react-bootstrap
- MUI

SQL

Restful API

- axios
- Express js

memory management systems

- Redux
- · Redux toolkit
- RTK Query

NoSQL Databases

MongoDB

version control system

Git

Linux administration

Skills (familiar)

SQL Databases

Socket IO

Jest

Professional Experience

Jun 2022 – present Tehran, Iran iApps, Front-end Developer ☑

- developing and maintaining the iApps store, developer panel, and backoffice projects
- developing both PWA and desktop sites
- working with Reactjs, TypeScript, react-hook-form, material UI, and RTK Ouerv
- · working with Jira and vivfyscrum
- making UI kit using storybook

Mar 2021 – Dec 2021 Mashhad, Iran team-x, Full Stack Engineer 🗈

- established a couple of full-stack projects, using MongoDB, node js, and react js
- experience with amazon aws3, zarin pal, and jwt
- implement mobile-first and responsive design
- experience writing API for android and working with UI UX designers
- versioning
- TDD test
- clean documentation
- server deployment for web app, API gateway, and document

Aug 2020 - Nov 2020 Mashhad, Iran

Bani Sanat Ertebat Rayan, Front End apprenticeship

- learning HTML, CSS, and Js
- an html based IOT project

Projects

iApps store developer panel

developing a new developer panel for iApps store developers. (desktop and mobile responsive)

iApps store 🛮

maintaining and developing the iApps store front-end

iApps landing page 🛮

maintaining iApps landing page

CRM ☑

a crm for mobile and desktop, full stack

Happypizza 🛮

ordering pizza online web app, mobile design

Happypizza Manager, happypizza project manager panel ☑

mobile base design

Smart Lock

IOT lock

Watering management 🛮

html base

Education

Aug 2019 – present

University of Tehran, Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Tehran, Iran

Languages

English fluent

Persian

mother tongue

Courses

Introduction to Front-End Development, $coursera.org \ \ \boxdot$

 $\textbf{Programming with JavaScript}, \textit{coursera.org} \ \ \boxdot$

 $\textbf{Version Control}, courser a. org \ \ \boxdot$